Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ashutoshtiwari-1089 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Management
Customer Service
Leadership

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Professional Working)

Certifications

C++

Honors-Awards

Best Mini Project award :Gesture controlled wheel chair with obstacle detection

Ashutosh Tiwari

Instrumentation engineer ,Innovative and hard working , willing to explore ,learn and apply the knowledge accquired .

New Delhi, Delhi, India

Summary

Experienced Assistant System Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Electronics & Instrumentation ,C++, SQL,MATLAB ,Electronics , Customer Service, Microsoft Word, and Public Speaking. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) focused in Instrumentation Technology from Siddaganga Institute of Technology ,Tumakuru.

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services
Former System Engineer
August 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 4 months)
New Delhi Area, India

Gill Instruments Limited Intern June 2016 - July 2016 (2 months)

bangalore

From 30th june 2016 to 30th july 2016..Responsibilities included to know about the MSP 430 controller and its various applications..to accquire more info regarding application areas of embedded systems..

Northern Coal Fields Itd.
Trainee
July 2015 - August 2015 (2 months)
Singrauli , Madhya Pradesh (India)

National Thermal Power Corporation Limited (Ntpc)
Trainee
July 2015 - July 2015 (1 month)
Madhya Pradesh, India

Education

Siddaganga Institute of Technology, TUMKUR

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Instrumentation Technology · (2012 - 2016)

Delhi Public School , Dhanbad AISSE, Mathematics · (2007 - 2011)

Delhi Public School , Nigahi (1998 - 2007)